IL Cafe we have you
covered welcome to Il Cafe my name is
shal and today we're going to be
catching up with a member of the ICI
Lombard family and that person is
abishek saraf and he's here to tell us
about two offerings and I'm quite
certain you'll walk away with more
information than you have right now as
we begin this conversation one of them
is called uh the Health Advantage policy
and the other one is be fit Rider so
both these are what we're going to be
catching up with abishek about well
thank you so much abishek and welcome to
Il Cafe thank you sh so certainly I will
explain you the both the benefit Health
Advantage and benefit we'll start with
Health Advantage first so Health
Advantage is a Comprehensive Health
insurance policy which cover all your
Healthcare needs so it has a cover from
impatient to occupation and also have an
IR like C personal exent and some of the
key benefit which include in this
product is a worldwide cover where we
cover both planned and unplaned
treatment then we have air ambulance
cover which is covered up to some
insured Home Care treatment where a
doctor has prescribed that the treatment
can be taken at home so this feature is
very useful and it was very useful at
time of CO as well then we have
unlimited Tel consultation where we
cover 247 Tel consultation a customer
can connect with the doctor 24 into 7
from I take care app we have a research
benefit which cover also same illness so
as you know C uh people buy a some in
short suppose I'm on average of 10 L
some in short and what happen happens if
that some insur exhaust during uh the
policy period so we have that unique
benefit research benefit for the same
inless a customer can basically top up
the Su insure from 10 plus 10 so that's
a great benefit a customer can have and
in addition to that we also have
guaranteed cumulative bonus so why it's
called granted is basically uh every
claim free year we give 20% of the summ
ins short as a bonus and in case a
customer claims so we don't deal with
anything so that's the reason we call it
granted So 20% every year maximum up to
100% okay now every customer have
different needs so everybody can opt for
different add-ons by paying extra
premium example M benefit which is
covered at a bding per of 9 months so
this again is a unique thing where uh in
the market people cover do such kind of
benefit of waiting period of couple of
three years but here we cover it after 9
months another thing where most of the
customer doesn't want to pay anything
out from the pocket in the hospital when
they go hospital at the time of
discharge there lot of La payables where
we the hospital the payment so now with
a add don't like claim protector a
customer can upt this cover and
basically non- payable will also be
covered in this policy right another
unique benefit here to beat inflation we
have a some insured Proctor a unique
cover where a guaranteed percentage of
some insured is increased every year for
example suppose the inflation rate is 7%
every year your 7% subm will increase
respective of the claim so there's
nothing to do with the claim it's just
to beat inflation right so these are the
host of coverage which we have in uh
Health Advantage policy which gives a
flexibility to the customer to make
their own plan and take the cover which
they need right yeah customer clearly at
the focus or the center of all that you
have uh thought of with respect to this
particular offering I can hear that
abishek and I really like the last point
you about beating inflation because
that's really on everybody's Minds uh
whether it is something like this a
topic we're discussing or you know
buying a home or anywhere at all but let
me come to this other reality that all
of us are in everything these days is
online right so why should someone
consider buying this um you know policy
the Health Advantage policy online what
happens everybody want to basically surf
online and to check each and every
benefit by their own so what happens so
when you go buy health insurance policy
online you have access to all the
information and also allow you to
compare the policies with other insurer
and a customer can take informed
decision that's the reason people go for
buying online policies so that they have
the more information and they can take
informed decisions well thank you for
that point it helps us understand what
the options are with respect to you know
getting hold of this particular policy
there's another one you mentioned be fit
Rider right at the start of our
conversation today so I think it's time
uh to get our viewers some insights on
what this is all about what is beit
Rider sure so so when we launch be rer
it was one of the unique I think
proposition in the market where we were
providing this OPD coverage which was
100% cashless digital solution so you
don't have to visit anywhere or you
don't have to basically go anywhere to
Avail such kind of benefit this can be
done through your home through the I
take care app so it allows policy holder
to have all the discussion with your
general physician specialist super
Specialist or I doctor also online and
this facility is available 24 into 7
okay so this product was kept in mind
that all your everyday Healthcare needs
apart from in patient hospitalization is
covered under this product so as we
already said it was a be is a beit rider
so on top of a base policy which you
have already taken you can buy this
cover okay and uh to add I just want to
add a couple of things more what are the
benefit which we have in beit cover so
to start with as I already said we have
outpatient service where we cover
physical doctor consultation also and we
also cover uh 24 into 7 tele
consultation other than that we cover
your Pharmacy cost diagnostic cost
physiotherapy session and also today I
think in today world most of the people
are operting such kind of feature like
diti and nutrition conseling so
everybody is conscious of the diet of
health and that facility available
through our I take
care absolutely and after the festive
season is over all the more reason to
actually focus on your diet that
particular angle is going to go for a
toss in sometime as all the sweets
really come out get rolled out uh you
know during navratri and certainly after
that in Diwali so useful pointer over
there but uh abishek tell me you know
how can someone Avail of this cashless
claim service for the beit rider and
also another question that I had in my
mind uh you mentioned base health
insurance policy to which this can be
you know add it on so which are the ones
from icsu Lombard that are eligible for
the B fet Rider so I come back to your
second question first so if you talk
about the base policy like the other
product also Golden Shield so all our
health uh inity policy retail can be
taken up with a B Rider so there's no
restrictions that this policy uh doesn't
have B rer all our Healthcare inmy
policy will have a b rer option to the
customers now coming to the first
question how we can Avil it so as I said
it's a 100% digital solution so to Avail
this Services you need to download I
take care app register and then select
the respective service icon on the app
homepage to assess the benefit for
example so if you Lo if you already have
a policy and if you log in with your
registered mobile number your policy
will be linked directly to app and on
the homepage you have a option like
telec consideration H so you can opt any
of the facility and you can Avail the
service so it's very uh I will say a
customer friendly uh app where you don't
require any kind of a basically
assistance so moving on right I want to
ask you a little bit more since you
mentioned dieticians um and we spoke
about that briefly a while ago as one of
the many categories little bit more I
think detail will be very helpful for
our viewers in terms of the kind of
healthcare professionals that they can
have access uh to Via this health
insurance
coverage yeah absolutely SE so we have a
wide range of doctors and medical
professional who are basically we have
done a tire start from the general
practitioner specialist super specialist
and I doctors so when we talk about
specialist we have seen the majority of
the take up in the consultation is from
specialist so like uh the people are
more ke like back pain shoulder pain so
people most of the people have availed
such kind of benefit apart from that we
have seen people have availed benefit
like for diabetes and hypertension which
are basically now a lifestyle kind of
disease where the most of the queries
has come across so what happen when we
have such kind of wide uh range of
doctors this ensure that they can
receive the care which every everyday
their health needs provide so now what
happens most of the people doesn't know
where to go to a such kind of benefit
like today I'm working in Mumbai maybe
I'm not not my home to so what happens I
don't know what kind of a specialist I
need or where where to go so such kind
of a product like bit Rider where we
provide 100% solution online uh the
customer can opt The Specialist as for
their choice so this give an opt option
to the customer so that they can Avail
the benefit as per the choice without
going
anywhere understood and that point that
you made is so true right a lot of us
actually work outside of our hometowns
now uh have moved to cities Etc and
access to healthcare professionals
sometimes that itself is a first
question mark right who do I seek out
and important to have raised that point
I imagine access to different
Specialists also as you underlined now
if you were to just summarize some of
the key benefits of both uh the
offerings that we spoke about the you
know Health Advantage policy and also be
for Rider what would you say to our
listeners so absolutely uh s what I like
to say definitely when you're looking
for a comprehensive health insurance
coverage which cover OPD as well as ipd
this both prod solution provided by
Lombard covers all the uh need of the
customer and top of that a customer uh
in case of they require a PA and CI
cover also like personal ex CI they can
opt as an add-on in Health Advantage so
no doubt uh if a customer is in India
and looking for a reliable HealthCare
coverage uh customer can opt for Health
Advantage and keep it D together well I
think that completes our understanding
of two offerings from the IC Universe in
is Cafe today and I'm super glad that
we're able to Spotlight you know
different offerings that we have that
have the customer at focus and address
some of the common pain points that
people have in their experience to seek
out good products in this particular uh
sector thank you so much for talking to
us abish and here's wishing you and your
family a very happy festive season uh
going forward in the best of health of
course thank you sh same to you it's
been a pleasure being here and sharing
the information to all our viewers